Memory Books Collection MS075
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Memory books, 1849 -- 1986; MS075.001; 47.57 Linear Feet; 2 Volumes; 1 Artifact(s)
  - Richard B. Parks scrapbook, 1933 -- 1935; MS075.000118 (Box 122)
    Richard B. Parks' Class of 1937 scrapbook, containing clippings, forms, invitations, pamphlets, tickets, and memorabilia.
  - Chi Alpha Chapter of Chi Omega, Scrapbook, 1938 -- 1945; MS075.001.073.001 (Box 73)
    Newspaper clippings, photos, letters, announcements, and misc. memorabilia
    Scrapbook; Chi Omega
  - Tufts Band, Scrapbook, 1940 -- 1959; MS075.001.075.001 (Box 75)
    Newspaper clippings, photos, announcements, and misc. memorabilia.
    Scrapbook; Department of Music
  - Jackson College Glee Club, 1942 -- 1948; MS075.001.114.00001 (Box 114)
    Jackson College; Glee Club; Odikon Singers
  - Scrapbook, 1943 -- 1944; MS075.001.051.001 (Box 51)
    Clippings regarding Tufts Medical School and its involvement with the war effort during World War II.
  - Edward Schluntz A'50, scrapbook, 1946 -- 1950; MS075.001.111.001 (Box 111)
    Newspaper clippings relating to the athletic career of Edward Schluntz A'50 while at Tufts.
  - Odikon Singers, Scrapbook, 1946 -- 1959; MS075.001.074.001 (Box 74)
    Newspaper clippings, articles, programs, and misc. memorabilia
    Scrapbook; Odikon Singers
  - Three memory books, 1950; MS075.001.002.001 (Box 2)
    Given by Connie Blanchard, belonging to Barbara Keane.
  - William R. Ransom, Mathematics publications scrapbook, 1950; MS075.001.050.001 (Box 50)
    Scrapbook of publications by William Ransom who taught mathematics at Tufts from 1900-1950.
    Scrapbook; Ransom, William R.
  - Thalia Sorority, Fall Pledge Class, Scrapbook, 1956 -- 1959; MS075.001.090.001 (Box 90)
    Photos, announcements, invitations, and misc. memorabilia
    Scrapbook; Thalia Sorority
  - Liz (Mirkin) Hawthorne, R1965, scrapbook, 1961-1965, MS075.001.119.00001 (Box Shared 8)
    Scrapbook of Liz (Mirkin) Hawthorne, Eliot-Pearson Class of 1965. Contains mostly ephemera relating to Hawthorne's 1961 graduation from high school and her time at Tufts University, 1961-1965. A wide variety of materials are represented, including paper ephemera, photographs, plant material, and cloth.
  - Tufts Dental School, Scrapbook, 1963 -- 1979; MS075.001.086.001 (Box 86)
    Newsclippings, photos, files, and misc. memorabilia.
  - Theater College, Scrapbook, MS075.001.070.001 (Box 70)
    List of plays; index to scrapbook
- Additional accessions, 1903 -- 1942; MS075.002
  - Charles F. K. Bean Class of 1907 scrapbook, 1903 -- 1907; MS075-001 (Box 1)
  - Charlotte Ginsberg's Jackson College Class of 1938 scrapbook, 1934 -- 1938; MS075-002 (Box 2)
  - Viola Ray's Jackson College Class of 1942 scrapbook, 1938 -- 1942; MS075-003 (Box 3)
  - Wilfred McKinney Class of 1926 scrapbook, 1922 -- 1926; MS075-004 (Box 4)
  - Barbara Leslie Badmington (Holden Yeomans) Class of 1937 scrapbook, MS075-005 (Box 5)
  - Virginia D. Rankin Class of 1920 scrapbook, MS075-006 (Box 6)